In the object window, select a type of fabric. In the attribute editor below, you can adjust the attribute of each fabric.
Click on the Open button next to the texture, and browse to select the texture image you need.
All versions of the fabric used will add textures.
By dragging the adjustment bar, adjust the texture intensity, the texture will be more obvious.
You can change the color and transparency of the fabric.
There are also high-light related settings below.
In Marvelous Designer, different fabric textures are expressed by physical properties.
We have provided a variety of fabric previews, which can meet all kinds of needs.
In general, fire-resistant fabrics are more smooth and smooth.
After opening the model, you can see that the properties of the application have different fabric effects.
When switching to wool fabric, you can see that the clothing becomes harder.
In the usual production process, the clothes are made in the same way.
In the usual production process, you can first use the default fabric as the basic sewing and modeling.
After completion, modify the fabric properties.
Below, you can modify some detail properties.
The strength of the gold sand, the tail sand, and the strength of the diagonal line are the stretching performance of the gold, tail, and diagonal lines of the fabric.
The higher the value, the more difficult it is to stretch.
In the adjustment process, if you need to withdraw, please press Ctrl Z.
The bending strength refers to whether the fabric is easy to bend.
The higher the value, the more difficult it is to bend the fabric.
The harder it looks, the harder it will be.
Before adding the zipper, please delete the original sewing line.
Use the Edit Sewing Line function to select the sewing line, then press the Delete button.
After opening the simulation, there is a gap between the panels.
You can add a zipper.
After selecting the zipper tool, click on the starting point.
Move the mouse in the direction of the zipper.
In the end position, double-click to create a side zipper.
The other side is operated in the same way.
The two sides of the zipper need to be aligned.
After opening the simulation, the zipper will be attached.
The front of the zipper is aligned.
When closing the simulation, use the move tool to select the zipper.
You can type the specific attribute in the parameter editor.
It can be adapted according to the attribute that needs to change width, thickness, and particle diameter.
The lower part can be modified to adjust the zipper pattern and color transparency.
It can also be modified to adjust the height setting and physical attribute.
When selecting the zipper head,
When selecting the head of the middle chain, you can type its attribute in the attribute editor, and you can modify its shape, proportion and weight.
When the hook selects the direction in which the chain is cut, the chain will be cut from the other direction.
When canceling the hook selection, the chain will be separated.
At this time, select to move to the reverse pull, the chain head will appear on the other side of the chain.
At the bottom, you can modify the strength, color and other attributes of the chain head.
When the hook is simulated, you can select and drag the chain head to adjust the position of the chain mechanism.
When the hook is simulated, the chain will be pulled apart.
Let's use the circuit divider to create a string on the panel line.
Click the starting point, and continue to click along the line of the created string to prevent adding to other lines.
In the end position, double click to complete the creation of the string.
A string will appear on the panel line after completion.
Use the tool to select the line to be edited.
After selecting the line, you can edit its width and particle diameter in the attribute editor.
You can modify its fabric at the bottom.
After adding a type of fabric to the object window, you can see that you can change the line fabric in the drop-down menu.
In the drop-down menu, you can adjust the width and particle diameter to the width of the object.
Select and change the falou at the top.
Click on the drop-down menu at the bottom of the top of the window to change the drop-down effect to yellow.
Select the point object with the drop-down tool and press the ground arrow key.
After selecting the bottom object, click on the drop-down button to select the horizontal axis.
You can see that the top of the icon has changed.
Press .